Guide to the Dance Pages Records,1930-1997, bulk 1982-1997
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1930-1997, undated, (3 boxes; 515 folders)
  - Dance Companies and Dancers, 1930-1997, undated, 432 folders
    - Mari Ushioda, undated (Box 3)
    - Madame Valentino: The Many Lives of Natacha Rambova by Michael Morris, undated (Box 3)
    - Wendy Van Dyck, undated (Box 3)
    - Martine Van Hamel, 1993, undated (Box 3)
    - David Van Tieghem, undated (Box 3)
    - Doug Varone and Dancers, undated (Box 3)
    - Vladimir Vassiliev and Ekaterina Maximova, undated (Box 3)
    - Viveca Vazquez, undated (Box 3)
    - Suzanne Vega, undated (Box 3)
    - Jac Venza, 1987, undated (Box 3)
    - Mary Verdi-Fletcher, undated (Box 3)
    - Phillippe Versen, undated (Box 3)
    - Roberto Villanueva, undated (Box 3)
    - Edward Villella, 1991-1992, undated (Box 3)
    - Adriano Vitale, 1982-1984, undated (Box 3)
    - Sara Vogeler, 1986, undated (Box 3)
    - Jeff Wadlington, undated (Box 3)
    - Bruce Walczyk, undated (Box 3)
    - Fats Waller, undated (Box 3)
    - Cathy Ward, 1984-1986, undated (Box 3)
    - Jessica Ward, undated (Box 3)
    - Douglas Wassell, undated (Box 3)
    - Cynthia Watts and Tommy D. Neblett, undated (Box 3)
    - Dennis Wayne, 1985-1989, undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Weidman, undated (Box 3)
    - Sharon Weiner, undated (Box 3)
    - Barry Weiss, 1976-1989, undated (Box 3)
    - Debra Weiss, undated (Box 3)
    - Tage and Lis Wendt, undated (Box 3)
    - Zita Wenzel, 1992, undated (Box 3)
    - George White Jr., 1986 (Box 3)
    - Michelle Wiles, 1995, undated (Box 3)
    - Williams Brothers, undated (Box 3)
    - Robin Williams, undated (Box 3)
    - Reginald Wilson, 1990-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Torsten de Winkel, undated (Box 3)
    - Ellis Wood-Iseyama, undated (Box 3)
    - Andrea E. Woods, undated (Box 3)
    - Charles Wright, undated (Box 3)
    - Eddie Wright, undated (Box 3)
    - Leni Wylliams, 1989, undated (Box 3)
    - Shannon Wyrrick, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
    - Setsuko Yamada, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Lorene Yarnell (for astrology), undated (Box 3)
    - Marlies Yearby, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Boris Yefimov and Igor Yurlov, undated (Box 3)
    - Keith Young, undated (Box 3)
    - Nina Youshkevitch, 1995-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Igor Youskevitch, 1982-1987, undated (Box 3)
    - Vanessa Zahorian, undated (Box 3)
    - Igor Zakharkin, undated (Box 3)
    - Stefa Zawerucha, undated (Box 3)
    - Eduardo Zeiger, undated (Box 3)
    - Yuri Zhukov, undated (Box 3)
    - Zowaki, undated (Box 3)
  - Dance-Related Topics, 1986-1995, undated, 13 folders
    The Dance-Related Topics subseries contains information pertaining to massage and physical therapy, hair and makeup, careers outside of professional dance, reviews of videos, television specials, and books, and other dance-related subjects. Materials include photographs, contact sheets, article drafts, correspondence, press releases, press clippings, and a coloring book.
    - Children's Television Workshop (Barkley), undated (Box 4)
    - Columbia - Life After Dance, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Dansource - Michael Gleason and Tauna Hunter, 1986, undated (Box 4)
    - Gary Glanzmen Massage Therapy, undated (Box 4)
    - Il Makiage, undated (Box 4)
    - PBS "Dancing" Series, 1993, undated (Box 4)
    - Physical Therapy photographs, undated (Box 4)
    - Pigeon (photos by John Rich, pianist - John Rich, go with Larry Stevens' article on Pigeon), undated (Box 4)
    - Sharon Strickler Sanchez coloring book review, 1990, undated (Box 4)
    - Dr. Terry L. Spilker, undated (Box 4)
    - Schmuel Tatz, undated (Box 4)
    - Video publicity photograph: Carmen with Antonio Gades and Laura Del Sol, undated (Box 4)
    - Video reviews, 1993-1995, undated (Box 4)
  - Events, Performances, and Venues, 1982-1997, undated, 31 folders
    The Events, Performances, and Venues subseries contains information pertaining to festivals, dance pieces, performances, dance competitions, theaters, and other arts venues. Materials include photographs, contact sheets, 35 mm slides, negatives, illustrated graphics, press clippings, press releases, press kits, brochures, article drafts, handwritten notes, and correspondence. Subjects of photographs are listed in the folder description when they differ from the folder title.
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1996, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photograph from Joseph Cashore's Lullaby and Other Stories.
    - Brooklyn Center for the Performing Arts, 1996-1997 (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Dance Theatre in Westchester, Roberta Flack, Marvin Hamlisch, New York Gilbert and Sullivan Players, Mazowsze, Stars of the Dance Theatre of Harlem/Alvin Ailey/Joffrey Ballet, and Wo'se Africa.
    - Brooklyn Dance Consortium, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photograph of Stacey Temple and Dancers.
    - La Cave, 1992-1993, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Ira Bernstein, Savion Glover, Ted L. Levy, Herbie Van Cayseele, and Van Porter.
    - Chinese Information and Culture Center, 1991, undated (Box 4)
    - Le Corsaire, undated (Box 4)
    - Crazy for You, undated (Box 4)
    - Dance Aspen Festival, 1993, 1996, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Ballet West, Eiko & Koma, Hubbard Street Dance Chicago, Lines Contemporary Ballet, Mark Morris Dance Group, Martine van Hamel's New Amsterdam Ballet, Parsons Dance Company, Pilobolus, and Rachel Rosenthal.
    - Dance Pages Fifth Anniversary Celebration Show at Limelight, 1988, undated (Box 4)
    - Die Etage, 1982-1987, undated (Box 4)
    - Festival of Korea, The Asia Society, 1992-1993, undated (Box 4)
    - Headliners Dance Competition, undated (Box 4)
    - Heart Strings - AIDS, 1992, undated (Box 4)
    - Hollywood East Bills, undated (Box 4)
    - The Imperial, undated (Box 4)
    - International Guild of Musicians in Dance - Celebrations in Collaboration, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photograph of composer/musician Gary Schall and dancer Rhonda Price.
    - International Women in Jazz - Harlem's Great Dancing Ladies, 1995-1997, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photograph of Clyde Wilder and Mickey Davidson.
    - Joyce Theater 10th Anniversary Season, 1992-1993, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of the Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company, Molissa Fenley, Erick Hawkins Dance Company, and Ralph Lemon Company.
    - The Kuopio Dance Festival, Suki John, 1986-1991, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Cumbre Flamenca, Gestos Transitonos, and Jorma Uotinen.
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, 1996, undated (Box 4)
      Contains publicity photographs for the Lincoln Center Festival 1996, Lincoln Center Out-Of-Doors, Midsummer Night Swing, and Mostly Mozart Festival.
    - Manchester Dance, 1996, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photograph of Bebe Miller.
    - Medford Dance Festival, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Millay Colony for the Arts, undated (Box 4)
    - New York Renaissance Festival, 1995-1996 (Box 4)
    - Rainbow Diner Theater, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Roseland, undated (Box 4)
    - Saratoga Performing Arts Center, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Spoleto Festival, 1996, undated (Box 4)
    - The Tap Dance Kid (Savion Glover), William Grey, Martha Swope, undated (Box 4)
    - Tap Dogs, 1997 (Box 4)
    - The Who's TOMMY, undated (Box 4)
  - Photographers, 1982-1989, undated, 11 folders
    The Photographers subseries contains photographs, contact sheets, a transparency, article drafts, paste-ups, brochures, flyers, invoices, handwritten notes, and correspondence. Subjects of photographs are listed in the folder description when they differ from the folder title.
    - Victor DeLiso, 1988, undated (Box 4)
    - David Fullard, 1985, undated (Box 4)
    - David Fullard photographs, 1982-1987, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of The Bronx Dance Theatre, Quentin Clark, Eiko & Koma, Eleo Pomare Dance Company, Charles Grant, Kenneth Hillard, Randy Howard, Saeko Ichinohe, Claire Iwatsu, Stanley Joseph, John Juhl, Charles Malik Lewis, Peggy Lyman, Patricia Page, Eleo Pomare, Thomas Reid, Evelyn Shepard, Peter Sparling, Ray Tadio, Osamu Uehara, George White Jr., and Leni Wylliams.
    - David Fullard: The Art of Photographing the Dance, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Lori Belilove, Pepsi Bethel, John Juhl, Bum-Ju Lee, Eun-Ju Lee, Sun Ock Lee, Charles Lewis, Evelyn Shepard, Osamu Uehara, and Leni Wylliams.
    - Jan LaSalle Photography, undated (Box 4)
    - Dianora Niccolini, 1985-1987, undated (Box 4)
    - Eduardo Patino, undated (Box 4)
    - Photographers, 1985, undated (Box 4)
      Contains information on Suellen Johnson and Jim Moore.
    - John Pregulman, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of William Soleau, Seung-Hae Joo, Christine Redpath, Chamber Ballet U.S.A.
    - Speliotis Photography, 1986-1989, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of Lisa Danias, Bob Fournier, Elisa King, Lawrence LeRitz, and Ken Romo.
    - Edward Swift, 1988-1989, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs of the New York City Ballet in The Unanswered Question.
  - Schools and Teachers, 1985-1996, undated, 7 folders
    The Schools and Teachers subseries contains photographs, negatives, and press releases. Subjects of photographs are listed in the folder description when they differ from the folder title.
    - American Academy of Ballet, undated (Box 4)
    - Bobby Blankshine - STEPS, 1985, undated (Box 4)
    - Oleg Briansky, undated (Box 4)
    - Vic D'Amore Studio of Dance, Inc., 1989, undated (Box 4)
    - Donya Feuer, 1995-1996, undated (Box 4)
      Contains photographs from The Dancer/Dansaren and of The Royal Dramatic Theatre of Sweden.
    - Sandy Hagan/Center, undated (Box 4)
    - Harid, undated (Box 4)
  - Visual Artists, Filmmakers, and Musicians, 1986-1995, undated, 15 folders
    The Visual Artists, Filmmakers, and Musicians subseries contains photographs of both artists and works of art, hand drawn cartoons, negatives, advertisement and article paste-ups, press clippings, brochures, flyers, programs, correspondence, resumes, biographical notes, and a magazine.
    - Jan De Ruth, undated (Box 4)
    - Tom Dooley, 1986, undated (Box 4)
    - Rusty Frank - Tap! The Tempo of America, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Tony Gatlif - Latcho Drom, undated (Box 4)
    - Philip Glass, undated (Box 4)
    - Shanton Granger cartoons, 1989, undated (Box 4)
    - Keith Gunderson, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Illustrators, 1986-1987, undated (Box 4)
      Contains information about Laurel Stern, Jimac, Ross Lewis, and Robert Lederman.
    - Carter Jones, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Young Uck Kim, 1994-1995, undated (Box 4)
    - Robert Lederman, 1986-1988, undated (Box 4)
    - Ross Lewis, 1986, undated (Box 4)
    - Paintings (Polaroids), undated (Box 4)
    - Phyllis Rudenjac, undated (Box 4)
    - Barbara Sandler, Nijinsky show, 1988-1989, undated (Box 4)
- Administrative Files, 1986-1995, undated, 29 folders
  The Administrative Files series holds records pertaining to a range of subjects. Some files contain materials related to magazine contributors, writers, and personnel, such as article drafts, poetry, timesheets, invoices, resumes, writing samples, and correspondence. Other files contain materials pertaining to business management, such as customer directories, invoices, professional correspondence, advertising leads, advertising solicitation letters, budgets, a two-year plan, and a history of Dance Pages. Additional materials include supply catalogs, brochures, photocopy request forms and receipts, magazine reply card layouts, personal correspondence, handwritten notes, press clippings, performance programs, a cooperative society newsletter, a magazine, photographs, and 35 mm slides.
  - Richard Aaron - The New Dance Horizon, 1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Natasha Baron, 1992, undated (Box 4)
  - Terence Guardino, undated (Box 4)
  - Hugh Harper, 1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Jacqueline Kolmes, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Denise Korn, 1987, undated (Box 4)
  - Labelworks, 1986, undated (Box 4)
  - Manual Landrove, 1988, undated (Box 4)
  - Lee's Construction, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Lawrence Leritz, 1989-1991, undated (Box 4)
  - Corinne P. Marquart, 1987-1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Cindy Nemser, undated (Box 4)
  - New York Public Library, 1991, undated (Box 4)
  - Notes (handwritten), undated (Box 4)
  - Karen N. Oujo, 1989 (Box 4)
  - PDG Art Gallery, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Jerry Perles, 1992-1993, undated (Box 4)
  - Personal Publishing magazine, 1986 (Box 4)
  - PETA - Treatment of Animals, undated (Box 4)
  - Photo labs, undated (Box 4)
  - Photofest, 1993 (Box 4)
  - Planners (catalog), 1987 (Box 4)
  - Poetry (Edward Patrick McCue, unlabeled), 1986, undated (Box 4)
  - Points of view clipping, undated (Box 4)
  - Reply card, undated (Box 4)
  - Ken Romo - Advertising Leads, 1987-1989, undated (Box 4)
  - Susan Tenaglie, 1994, undated (Box 4)
  - Three Arrows Cooperative Society, 1993-1995 (Box 4)
  - Dr. Dorothy Whipple, 1995 (Box 4)